Guide to the University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.) University Relations Records 1930-2012
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Biographical Information, 1937-1983; Series III
  - Williams, Pat (Congressman), 1982; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/95)
  - Willmering, William Joseph, 1967-ca.1968; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/96)
  - Wilson, Brenda F. (Mrs), 1937-1966; affiliation: Chairman of Business Education and Office Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/97)
  - Wilson, Paul B., 1971; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/98)
  - Wilson, Penelope A. (Penny), 1969; affiliation: Radio and TV (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/99)
  - Wilson, Ralph A., 1973; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/100)
  - Wingard, Gordon G., ca. 1969; affiliation: Philosophy (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/101)
  - Winnie John, 1972; affiliation: Philosophy (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/102)
  - Winston, Ralph J., ca. 1969; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/103)
  - Winterowd, W. Ross, 1962, 1964; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/104)
  - Witt, Daniel, 1961, 1967; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/105)
  - Wooden Legs, John, 1971, 1978; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/106)
  - Woodruff, Julian, 1974; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/107)
  - Woodward, Leslie J., ca. 1968; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/108)
  - Woolhiser, Dale, 1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/109)
  - Woolston, Wayne C., 1970-1973; affiliation: Registrar (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/110)
  - Worden, Henry O. "Bill", 1970; affiliation: Missoula Banker / Archive Donor (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/111)
  - Worring, Ray, 1971-1972; affiliation: Director Technical Assistance Bureau (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/112)
  - Wren, Melvin C. Dr., 1956-1967; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/113)
  - Wright, Benjamin W., 1965-1968; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/114)
  - Wright, Mark Joseph, 1975; affiliation: Student Affairs Assistant (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/115)
  - Wright, Phillip, 1943-1981; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/116)
  - Wriht, Ralph S., 1969-1973; affiliation: Research Associate - Office of Vice President for Research (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/117)
  - Yates, Dwight Alan, 1971; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/118)
  - Yates, Leland M., 1959-1972; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/119)
  - Yee, Albert, 1979-1982; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/120)
  - Zacek, Joyce, 1973-1977; affiliation: Graduate School (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/121)
  - Zimmermann, Robert R., 1969-1973; affiliation: Psychology (Box-folder Series 3 - 6/122)